《法外情真》前情提要
Previously on The Guardian.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我不在乎你想不想嫁给我
I don't care if you don't want to marry me.
我知道我做好当爸爸的准备了
I know that I'm ready to be a father.
那么多的家长  都会让孩子失望
So many parents fail their children.
听着  我不是同性恋
Look, I'm not gay.
匹兹堡是个小地方
Pittsburgh is a small town.
议论我
Talking about me...
祝贺你完成了戒断程序
Congratulations for completing your program.
关于我们的事儿
About us...
- 如果你能就试着  - 试一试吗
- if you could try to just... - Try?
对  试一试
Right... try.
- 嗨  - 嗨  外面真冷啊
- Hey. - Hi. It's freezing.
是啊
Yeah.
现在很晚了  你还好吗
It's, um-- It's late. You-- You okay?
抱歉  我不好  我  我睡不着
I'm sorry. No, l, uh-- I just couldn't sleep.
好吧
That's all right.
要不要来杯茶
Um, you want some tea or something?
好啊
Yeah.
孩子出了点问题
There's a problem with the baby.
什么问题
What kind of problem?
唐氏综合症
Down syndrome.
三倍显示检查的时候
I got the results of my triple marker screening,
显示这个孩子可能有
and, uh, it indicated that there could be
得唐氏综合症的可能
some kind of a problem like this with the baby,
所以为了搞清楚情况  我做了羊水检测  今天结果出来了
so I had to go ahead and get an amnio, and I got those results today.
之前为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
因为在不确定之前  我不想因为
Because I just didn't want to bother you
这种事情打扰你
with something like this until I knew for certain.
好吧  好吧  现在确定了吗
Right. Right. Well, is it for certain?
羊水测试有百分之九十九的可能
Amnio. It's 99%.
呃  医生
Um, the doctor...
给了我这个
gave me this.
但是我不知道这个到底有没有用
I mean, I don't know how much it's really gonna help.
我现在都不知道我要什么了
I don't-- I don't even know what I really want right now.
是啊
Right.
我是说  我不知道我们能不能接受拥有一个这样的小孩
I mean, I don't know that we can handle having a child like this.
我们
''We''?
对
Right.
我先走了  明天再说吧
I'm gonna go. Let's talk about it tomorrow.
好的
All right.
嗯
Okay.
第三季  第十四集
法外真情
翻译   马   丁
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
所以当时在吃晚饭
So, we sit down to dinner
门铃响了
and the doorbell rings.
我没有在意
I ignore it,
但是门铃一直响  有人在一直敲门
but it keeps ringing, and somebody keeps knocking.
所以我去开门了  结果是两个警察
So I go to answer it, and these two cops come into my house
和两个社会服务的女人来了
with two women from Social Services.
蒂尔登先生  等我一下
Mr. Tilden, can you just give me one second?
我一会儿就来
One second.
你知道  我确实犯了一个错
You know, just 'cause I've made mistakes--
我也知道我犯错了  但是露露
Now, I know that I've made mistakes, but, Lulu,
我觉得不管遇到什么问题我们都能一起解决
I think that we can work out whatever problems we have.
所以千万不要因为我们现在的关系影响了你的决定
So just don't let us interfere with this decision.
过去的已经过去了  尼克
Well, the past is prologue, Nick.
已经发生的我也不能当它没发生
You know, all I have to go on is what's been.
所以很感谢你对我说这样的话
So you can say these things. It's nice. Thank you.
- 但是这改变不了任何事 - 我说什么都没用了吗
- But it doesn't really change anything. - Does what I say have any bearing?
- 这跟我一点关系都没有吗  - 当然有
- Am I not involved in this? - Of course.
好吧
Okay.
医生有没有跟你说我们还有多长时间
The doctor tell you how much time we have?
- 我已经处于孕中期了  - 但是我们还有时间吗
- I'm in my second trimester, so-- - But do we have any time?
没有了
Not really.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
嗨  我已经等了一早上了
Hey, I've been waiting all morning.
我得回去
I gotta get back to...
尼克
Nick?
我没事
I'm fine.
如果你想要谈谈的话
lf you need to talk--
没事  我没事
No, I'm fine.
那好吧
Okay.
孩子有唐氏综合症
The baby has Down syndrome.
你来读一读这篇文章
And you, uh-- you read this material,
上面就是些没用的话  你知道吗
and it's all just words, you know?
多一条染色体  心脏缺陷  发育迟缓
Just extra chromosome, heart defects, retardation...
只是些介绍罢了
It's just all words.
如果需要我的话
lf there's anything I can do...
谢谢你
Thank you.
蒂尔登先生
Mr. Tilden?
社会服务说他们接到了一个电话
So, Social Services said they got a call
有人举报我  说我性侵了我自己的女儿梅根
that someone had accused me of molesting my daughter, Megan,
他们告诉我要在我家查一查
and they told me I had to let them look around.
接着警察就让我坐在角落里的沙发上
Next thing I know, the cops have me on the couch in the corner
然后带走了我的女儿们
and they took the girls.
- 你有三个女儿啊  - 嗯  梅根  辛迪和艾米
- You have three girls? - Megan, Cindy, and Amy.
- 她们现在在哪里  - 在她们的爷爷奶奶家
- Where are they now? - At their grandparents'.
- 你爸妈家吗  - 我岳父岳母那儿
- Your parents? - My wife's.
- 你太太呢  - 在县医院
- Where's your wife? - At the county hospital.
- 她什么时候能出院  - 不
- When does she get out? - She doesn't.
她已经昏迷了好几年了
She's been in a coma for four years,
所以她出不了院
so she doesn't get out.
那么今天下午在法庭见  住所听证会三点开始
So, I'll meet you outside the courthouse at 3:OO for the shelter hearing.
谢谢
Thank you.
没事
Okay.
尼克
Nick.
残疾人之家
The Home for the Developmentally Disabled.
我们已经代理他们超过十年了
We've been representing their residents for over a decade.
然后呢
Right.
有个23岁的患有唐氏综合症的孩子
So, there's this 23-year-old kid with Down syndrome.
我本来是要帮他解决遗嘱的问题的
I'm supposed to help him deal with a probate issue.
- 哦  - 如果你想要的话  这个案子就交给你了
- Okay. - If you want, you can take it.
给我
Me?
你说过  这不过是书面的话罢了  对吗
You said it was all just words, right?
是遗嘱的事情吗
It's a probate issue?
先生们  很高兴大家今天能赏脸过来
Gentlemen, it's good to have you with us today.
现在  正如你们所知  里弗布鲁克乡村俱乐部
Now, as you may know, the Riverbrook Country Club
是匹兹堡最古老最有声望的俱乐部之一
is one of Pittsburgh's oldest and most prestigious.
我们的会员涵盖了商务精英  政治领袖以及知名慈善家
Our members include leaders in business, politics, and philanthropy.
每一年我们都期待会见
Every year, we look forward to meeting
一些正式会员候选人
a select number ofjunior member candidates.
我们已经从你们的赞助商那边听到了很多关于你们的好消息
We've heard good things about all of you from your sponsors.
所以我们期待在你们申请会员的过程中能
So now we look forward to getting to know you better
更加深入地了解你们
during your application process.
请随我前往花园
Follow me out to the garden.
杰克
Jake?
凯特  嗨
Kate. Hey!
- 你来这儿干嘛  - 我只是来参观的
- What are you doing here? - Oh, uh, just orientation.
- 你懂的  我想融入  - 好极了
- You know, I was trying to join. - Great.
也许我可以喜欢高尔夫和网球
Yeah, you know, maybe-- I like golf and tennis.
所以  你是会员吗
So, are you, uh-- are you a member?
我的高曾祖父之前帮忙建立了这地方  所以
Oh, my great-great-grandfather helped found the place, so...
是吗
Really?
是啊  我知道这很蠢
Yeah. I know it's stupid.
所以你现在是要去办聚会吗
Um, so is it a party?
是露露的孩子的婴儿欢迎会
Lulu's baby shower.
你们要在这里举办啊
Oh. You're having it here.
- 是的  周三下午  - 哦  太好了
- Yeah. Wednesday afternoon. - Oh, that's nice.
你知道的  上个
You know, that was, uh--
上个感恩节很有意思
that was fun last Thanksgiving-- the, uh--
橄榄球赛
the Turkey Bowl at the Point.
是啊
Yeah.
- 你玩得真不错  - 谢谢
- You played really well. - Thanks.
我要去把这些放下  然后去找供应餐饮的人谈一谈
Well, I have to, um, drop this off and talk to the caterer.
好的好的  听着
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um, uh, listen,
如果你有空的话  我想请你吃午饭
you know, maybe if you have some time, maybe I could buy you lunch.
什么时候
When?
等你有空
Whenever you're free.
- 我今天就有空  - 好的
- Well, I was gonna eat here today, - Okay.
你要不要跟我一起吃
if you'd like to join me.
- 哦  在这儿吃啊  - 嗯
- Oh, eat here. - Yeah.
- 太好了  - 那我们待会儿在这里见
- Great. - So, I'll just meet you back here?
- 好的好的  那我  好  - 好极了
- Yeah, yeah. I'll-- Okay. - Great.
好的  太好了
All right. Great.
- 你是尼克·法林吗  - 我是
- Nick Fallin. - Right.
- 我是汉克  - 你好
- Hank. - Hi.
- 你能这么快就来太好了  - 没事
- It's good of you to come so quickly. - Oh, it's no problem.
你以前有没有跟像马克这样的人一起工作过
So, have you worked with people like Mark before?
有过一两次
Once or twice.
那你应该理解这会有点让人泄气
Then you understand it can be a bit frustrating.
他的妈妈在遗嘱里给他留了一万五千美元
Okay. His mother left him $15,000 in her will.
但是这点钱只能维持他一年的生计
That's not enough to last for more than a year,
但是这些钱会使他失去获得社会保障的资格
but it's gonna disqualify him from his Social Security.
嗯
Right.
所以我们为他建立信任担保  这样他就不会失去社保资格了
So we need some help setting up a trust so he's not disqualified.
好的
Okay.
否则的话要不了几个月他就会流落街头了
Otherwise he can end up on the street for a few months.
马克
Mark?
马克  这是尼克·法林
Mark, this is Nick Fallin.
尼克  这是马克
Nick, Mark.
嗨
Hi.
你快看看这个车啊
Look at this car.
尼克会帮你解决问题的
Nick's going to help you with your problem.
你会不会开车啊
You know how to drive?
我会
Yeah, I do.
所以我要跟他讲讲整个流程吗
So, do I just explain to him the process?
- 当然  - 好的
- Sure. - Okay.
马克
Mark.
Mark!
喂  我在看车车呢
Hey, I look at that.
尼克会跟你讲他会怎么帮你
Nick's gonna tell you how he's gonna help you.
马克  你妈妈去世的时候
Mark, uh, when your mother died, she--
我妈妈每天帮我刷牙  帮我刷牙
My mother brush me, brush my teeth,
帮我洗头
wash my hair.
是啊  那她去世的时候  她给你留了
Right. Uh, when she died, she left you--
她想让我学认字
She want me to learn to read.
让他集中注意力需要花点时间
It takes him some time to get focused.
那么  马克  我会为你准备一些东西
Well, Mark, I'm gonna set something up for you
这样就不会失去保险了
so that you don't lose your insurance.
我超喜欢表演的
I love acting.
很棒啊
That's nice.
我演了
I acted.
很多特殊的人物
Very special players.
很好
Good.
汉克  你这儿有没有房地产的信息
Hank, do you have the estate information?
- 有的  我这就去拿  - 谢谢
- Sure. I'll go get it. - Thank you.
我演了帕克
I played Puck.
是吗
Really.
如果
''lf--
如果我们影子
''lf we shadows
冒犯了
''has offended,
想想但是这一切
''think but this is all--
这一切
''is all--
这
iS''--
- 被愈合了  - 对
- Is mended? - Right.
- 被愈合了  - 好吧
- ''ls mended.'' - Okay.
有事吗
Yeah?
嗨  伯顿  我只是想为里弗布鲁克俱乐部
Hey, Burton, I just wanted to say thank you again
的事再次表示感谢
for setting that up at Riverbrook.
哦  没事
Oh. Yeah, sure.
你喜欢那里吗
You liked it?
所以你要申请会员吗
So, you, uh-- you want to apply?
我可以打电话安排一下
I can make some calls.
好的  太好了
All right. Good.
你知道那边还有谁可以帮得上你吗
You know anybody else out there that might be able to help you?
额  只有凯特·肖
Well, only Kate Shaw.
好
Okay.
她是理查德·肖的女儿吗
Richard Shaw's daughter?
是的  事实上我们今天一起吃午饭了
Yeah, we, uh-- we actually had lunch today.
我想除了吃午饭  你也不能做其他事了吧
You can't do much better than that, I guess.
我们今天约好了要一起吃晚餐
We're-- We're gonna have, uh, dinner again tonight.
格雷夫斯小姐  你认为如果让孩子回家的话
Miss Graves, you believe returning the children to their home
她们会有危险吗
would place them in imminent danger?
我们接到的举报电话里把性侵的事实描述得很详细
The phone call alleging sexual abuse was specific,
蒂尔登先生也非常地不配合我们
and Mr. Tilden has been uncooperative with us.
蒂尔登先生以前从来没有虐待或者冷落过孩子
Mr. Tilden has no history of child abuse or neglect.
肖小姐  你的意见是
Miss Shaw?
孩子们跟祖父母一起住很自在
The children are comfortable with their grandparents.
在社会服务调查完之前她们不会遭受伤害
They won't be traumatized while Social Services completes their investigation.
但是  标准并不是她们会不会受到伤害
Well, the standard is not whether they're traumatized.
我宣布  在社会服务调查清楚指控之前
I'm placing these children with their grandparents
孩子暂时和祖父母一起住
until Social Services has finished evaluating this allegation.
电话就是他们打的
They made the call.
他们为什么要这么做
Why would they do that?
因为我不允许他们见我的女儿
Because I don't let them see my daughters.
两年前我想放弃我太太的治疗  他们反对我的做法
I wanted to let my wife die two years ago, and they opposed me.
把我告上了法庭
Tied it up in the courts.
我最后倾家荡产  一无所有
Cost me everything I had.
蒂尔登先生  社会服务想要继续调查
Mr. Tilden, Social Services wants to continue this investigation.
我是说  她得了肺炎  将近三个星期
I mean, she's had pneumonia for almost three weeks.
- 他们每次要给她的肺吸气两次  - 蒂尔登先生
- They vacuum her lungs twice a day. - Mr. Tilden.
我在听
I'm listening.
他们要求你去见一见精神病专家
They're gonna ask you to speak with a psychiatrist
检查下你是否有性功能障碍
to determine if you have a sexual disorder.
我从未碰过梅根
I never touched Megan.
那就按要求的做吧
Then just cooperate with their requests.
你还好吗
Is everything all right?
凯特·肖计划
You know, uh, Kate Shaw planned
在这周三为我的孩子举行欢迎会
this big baby shower for me on Wednesday afternoon.
我刚要打电话给她让她取消这么蠢的计划
I just picked up the phone to call her and cancel the whole stupid thing.
嗯
Right.
但是我做不到
And, uh, l-- I couldn't do it.
我不能取消这个欢迎会
I mean, I couldn't cancel the party.
我还做不到
I just-- I couldn't do it yet.
如果我们影子
''lf we shadows
冒犯了
''have offended,
想想这个
think this''--
再试一次
Try it again.
遗嘱检验法庭将允许我们创造一种叫做特殊需要信托的东西
The probate court will allow us to create something called a Special Needs Trust.
你可以作为受托者  也可以由你指定一家银行
You can act as trustee, or you can appoint a bank
或者残联来受托
or the Disability Alliance to do so.
然后他的社保就会继续下去了吗
So his Social Security won't be discontinued?
- 不冒犯了  -  是冒犯了
- ''...have 'befended'''-- - ''Omended.''
- 对  - 好的
- Right. - Great.
我们所有的材料都在社保局
We have all the paperwork at LSP,
如果你今天下午可以去那边的话  我们就可以开始了
so if you come in there this afternoon, we can get started.
好的  好的
Great. Okay.
- 我们再试一次  - 再见
- Try it again. - I'll see you later.
- 我们  - 如果
- ''We''--  - ''lf.''
我是说  如果我们影子
I mean, ''lf we shadows
冒犯了
''have offended,
想想但是这个
think but this''--
这一切
''And alI''.. .
都会被愈合
''And all is mended.''
非常棒
Very good.
- 我还行吗  - 你太棒了
- I'm good? - You're very good.
我有点累了
I'm tired.
好吧  马克
Okay, Mark.
理查德先生  你能来药房一下吗
Ms. Richards, can you come to the dispensary?
Ms. Richards, you're needed over at the dispensary.
你的表演是在几号啊
When's your show on?
我在18号
The show on the 18th,
17号  14号
1Tth, 14th,
还有15号表演
and then 15th.
那可是要买票的
It's not for free.
好的
Okay.
马克  你知不知道你妈妈给你留了一笔钱
Mark, you understand that your mother Ieft you some money?
这笔钱你有没有特别想做的事
ls there anything special that you want to do with it?
我想买辆车
I want to get a car.
好吧  我在想你用这些钱来做一些切合实际的事
Well, I was thinking more along the lines of, uh,
比如存起来  也许将来有一天你就可以自食其力了
saving it so that one day you can live on your own.
我想买辆车
I want to get the car.
我喜欢开车
I like to drive.
好吧
Right.
我能问你一个问题吗
Can I ask you something?
得了唐氏综合症的感觉怎么样
What's it like to have Down syndrome?
我只是多了一条染色体
I got an extra chromosome.
是啊  你多了一条染色体  我知道
Right. You have an extra chromosome. I understand that.
我想要开车
I want to drive.
好吧
Okay.
我有女朋友
I got girlfriend.
我快要有孩子了
Gonna take care of a baby.
我们学校每周五放学都有滑雪俱乐部
My school has a ski club. Right after school on Fridays,
大家都坐公交去七泉镇或者希登瓦利
everybody takes a bus up to Seven Springs or Hidden Valley.
嗯
Right.
大家都带着自己的滑雪装备去体育馆  知道吗
Everyone brings their ski stuff to gym, right?
梅根
Megan.
好吧
Right.
我总是
I always...
每周五  我总是靠着墙看着这些
Fridays. I always looked atthe stuff up against the wall.
我是说  我从来没有滑过雪
I mean, I've never even been skiing.
自从妈妈生病之后我甚至没有滑过雪撬
I haven't even gone sledding since my mom got sick.
我问我爸我能不能去一次  他说不行
I asked my dad if I could go just once, and he said no.
我只是想去一次
I just wanted to go once.
- 她撤回了吗  - 是的
- She's recanted? - Correct.
那就把孩子送回去吧
Well, then, send the kids home.
没那么简单
It's not so simple.
虽然虐待的指控没有了  但是我们却有明显的被冷落的证据
The abuse allegations were false, but there's clear evidence of neglect,
而且蒂尔登先生否认了家里发生的事情
and Mr. Tilden's in denial about what's going on in his home.
- 什么意思  - 一直是梅根在照顾
- What do you mean? - Megan Tilden takes care
她的两个妹妹  因为蒂尔登先生不照顾她们
of her younger sisters because Mr. Tilden will not.
大部分时间是梅根一个人照顾她的两个妹妹
And for the most part, she's parenting her younger sisters alone.
我们还发现梅根今年已经旷课30天
We also found that Megan missed 30 days of school this year,
去年她还留级了
and she was held back last year.
好吧  本次指控是性侵
All right. The issue here is alleged sexual abuse.
梅根非常沮丧地指控了这种虐待
The fact that Megan was upset enough to allege that kind of abuse
其他问题也应该被认真对待
suggests these other issues be taken very seriously.
所以如果我的当事人同意梅根去参加滑雪俱乐部是不是问题就解决了
So if my client allows Megan to join the ski club, everything's gonna be okay.
我的当事人不应该负责
My client does not want to be responsible
照顾抚养她的妹妹
for the care and upbringing of her sisters.
- 她想让他爸爸意识到这个问题  - 好吧
- She'd like her father to know that. - All right.
我们在讨论一个跟本案完全不相关的问题
Well, we're talking about a completely separate issue here.
她就因为不想再照看家里的事情就说我性侵了她？
She's tired of helping out at home so she said I was molesting her?
她只是想要一个正常的生活
She just wants a normal life.
我们再也不能正常生活了
None of us have a normal life anymore.
你看看她
Look at her.
- 蒂尔登先生  - 梅根说她不想做晚饭了吗
- Mr. Tilden-- - Megan doesn't like cooking dinner?
我知道了
I get it.
她帮我照顾艾米和辛迪太累了
She's tired of helping out with Amy and Cindy--
蒂尔登先生  你应该为孩子提供一些照顾
Mr. Tilden, you need to provide some sort of child care.
梅根不明白的是  我得挣钱养家
What Megan doesn't understand is what I have to do to keep this family going.
我做着两份工作
I work two jobs.
我一天还要来两趟这里  确保
I'm here twice a day to make sure that no one--
没有人忘记什么事
no one forgets anything.
我要防止她褥疮  我要给她擦身子
It's bedsores and cleaning,
我要看着她的饲管
feeding tubes,
给她洗头
washing her hair.
总得有人要做这些事吧
Somebody's gotta do that.
嗨
Hi.
Hey.
现在说话方便吗
ls it a bad time?
你说吧  你还好吗
No. How you doing?
好吧  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我一直在想这一切都不是真的
I keep thinking it's not real, you know?
露露  我主动接下了一个案子
Lulu, uh, I volunteered for this case, uh,
我想试着去
I guess, to try and...
去理解我们可能会遇到的情况
have more of an understanding of what we may be facing.
然后呢
Okay.
这个案子里的这个孩子得了唐氏综合症
I'm working with this kid that has Down syndrome.
他因为遗嘱的事情  我要带他出席法庭
He has a probate issue, and I'm gonna take him to court,
我要帮他建立一个新的信托
and I'm gonna set him up with a new trust.
- 我不太明白  - 他现在就在那间办公室
- I don't understand. - He's in the office now.
如果你看到我和他在一起  我不想让你认为
So when you see him with me, I just didn't want you to think
我是故意做给你看
that I was trying to make some kind of point.
哦  你把一个患有唐氏综合征的孩子带到我们办公室
Oh, you bring a kid with Down syndrome into my office,
然后你告诉我让我不要想太多
and then you tell me that you're not trying to make a point?
我只是想告诉你而已
I just-- I just wanted to tell you.
好的  马克一切都搞定了
Okay. So, uh, Mark's all set.
他的社保不会被取消了
His Social Security benefits won't be affected,
你要负责维持他的信用
and you'll be responsible for the upkeep of his trust.
- 好的  - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
额  马克  好好谢谢法林先生吧
Uh, Mark, you should thank Mr. Fallin.
- 谢谢你  - 不客气  马克
- Thank you. - You're welcome, Mark.
汉克要带我去看电影
Hank gonna take me to the movies.
好的
Good.
和我的朋友一起
With my friends.
好的
Good.
上次  我买了爆米花
Last time, I had popcorn,
结果掉在地上了
l-- I dropped it.
嗨  马克
Hey, Mark.
- 你忘了说再见了  - 再见
- You forgot to say good-bye. - Bye.
再见
Bye.
再见了  鳄鱼叔叔
See you later, alligator.
昨天是不寻常的一天
Yesterday was unusual.
是啊
Yeah.
午饭  晚餐  晚餐后的事
Lunch, dinner, after dinner.
不同寻常
It was unusual.
等等  你是要跟我分手吗
Wait. Are you-- Are you breaking up with me?
不  我只是
No, I just--
什么
What?
这是我们这两天的第三次约会了  杰克
Look, this is our third date in two days, Jake.
我只是  我还不太了解你
I just-- I don't really know anything about you.
好吧  你想要知道什么
Well, what do you want to know?
这又不是采访
This isn't an interview.
嗯  我知道
Oh, I know that.
我不太擅长处理感情的事
I'm pretty good at screwing up relationships,
因为我34岁了还单身
judging by the fact that I'm 34,
一周工作70个小时  而且我甚至都没有养猫
and I work 70 hours a week, and I don't even have a cat.
嗯
Right.
我爸妈很喜欢我上一个男朋友
My father and mother Ioved my last boyfriend--
一个旧贵族
this old-money guy.
我们两分分合合
It kind of worked, kind of didn't.
一起去旅游
Traveled.
每天都奉承我爸
Kissed my father's ass on a daily basis.
- 好吧  - 但是那不是我啊
- Okay. - That's not me.
听着  我是说
Look, what I'm saying is,
我不想跟你一起去乡村俱乐部
I don't want to go to the country club with you.
- 好的  - 我不喜欢那里的世界  我从来没有喜欢过
- Okay. - I don't like that world. I never did.
但是  呃
But, uh,
但是因为我以前在那里  我希望
uh, just 'cause I was there, I mean, l-- I hope--
我希望你不会觉得我是因为那样才喜欢你
I just hope you don't think I like you because of that.
你真的不是那个俱乐部的料
Oh. Well, you're hardly the country club type.
所以  我们没事了
So, um, we're good?
是的
Yeah.
有件事我想跟你说
There's just one other thing that I wanted to ask you.
你说吧
Yeah, anything.
我需要你在我们那个之前
I need you to take an HIV test
去做一下艾滋测试
before things lead where they do.
我也会去做
And I'll take one, too.
我让你不舒服了
Oh, I've made you uncomfortable and...
抱歉
Oh, uh, excuse me.
好吧
Okay.
嗨
Hi.
好吧
Okay.
好的  露露
Okay, Lulu.
我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry.
你不用再说了
You don't have to say anything else.
好吧  那我待会儿再打给你
Okay, I'll call you later.
怎么了
What is it?
是
It's...
- 露露取消了孩子的欢迎会  - 为什么
- Lulu just cancelled the baby shower. - Why?
你们来猜猜是谁  好吗
You fellas try and guess who's the-- who's it, okay?
那么看好了
Okay, watch.
- 比尔  - 什么
- Bill. - What?
- 我们来  - 好
- Let's do it. - Hey.
你们在看吗  各位
You watching, fellas? You got it?
杰瑞
Jerry.
现在你来试一试
Come. You try it now.
法林先生  有事吗
Mr. Fallin. Hey. Something wrong?
没事  我有个想法
Uh, no, no. I just-- I had this idea.
我在报纸上看到这条广告  他们在为
I saw this ad in the paper. They're auditioning this week
夏季莎士比亚戏剧节进行试镜
for the summer Shakespeare festival.
你知道的  这些都是剧目  要招募专业演员
You know, it's regular plays with professional actors,
但是每年他们也会招募一些
and each year they, uh, employee a few people with, um...
- 残疾人吗  - 是的
- Disabilities? - Right.
我想
And, uh, you know, I just thought
马克有可能会对这个感兴趣
it might be something that Mark would be interested in.
如果马克想去的话  我很乐意带他去
lf he wants to do it, I'd be happy to take him.
- 好的  我会告诉他的  - 好的
- Okay. I'll let him know. - All right.
- 嗨  - 杰克  你来干什么
- Hey. - Jake. What are you doing here?
你给凯特打电话说孩子
I was, um, with Kate Shaw
的事情的时候  我就在旁边
when you called and told her about the baby.
她告诉你了
She told you.
太好了
That's great.
你跟凯特在一块干什么
What were you doing with Kate?
我们在  呃
Uh, l-- I've kind of been, uh...
我们在约会
Well, we've kind of been dating.
我是想来说我很抱歉听到这个消息
But l-- I just wanted to say how, uh, sorry I am,
如果我能帮上你什么忙的话
and, uh, if there's anything I can do to help.
你在跟凯特约会吗
Y-You're dating Kate?
是的
Right.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing.
- 怎么了  - 好吧  杰克
- What? - Well, Jake--
- 怎么了啊  - 杰克  得了吧
- What? - Jake, come on.
听着  我不是来和你说这个事的
Look, you know, l-- l-- I really didn't come here to talk about that.
- 好吧  - 我只是想说如果你有
- All right. - I just wanted to know if you were--
- 我没事的  - 是吗
- I'm okay. - You are?
嗯  谢谢  但是我真的没事
Yeah. Thanks, but I'm okay.
好吧
Okay.
杰克
Jake.
你知道  凯特·肖跟我是很好的朋友
You know, Kate Shaw's a very good friend of mine.
知道
Right.
卡尔认为我们大家坐下好好试着
Carl felt it was important
去解决问题比较好  而不是去法庭
to try and work this out instead of having to go to court.
卡尔  你开始吧
So, Carl.
梅根
Megan,
我之前
I was...
对你所做的事感到很生气
pretty upset about what you did.
嗯
Right.
我是说  我不知道你以前是怎么想的
I mean, I didn't know you felt the way you felt,
我真希望你能来找我好好聊聊
and I guess I just wish you had talked to me about it.
我试过跟你好好聊
I tried to talk to you.
一直抱怨要照顾两个妹妹并不是好好聊
Complaining about taking care of your sisters isn't exactly talking.
对不起  对不起  你这么做就是为了滑雪旅行的事情吗
I'm sorry-- I'm sorry. This is about a ski trip?
你们这些人  根本没有办法理解我们这种人的生活
You people have no idea what it's like to be us.
知道吗  没有办法理解
Okay? No idea.
- 卡尔  - 他们就是不理解
- Carl-- - They don't.
他们一点儿也不理解
They don't have any idea!
梅根  我很抱歉  但是你这样真的太不懂事了
And, Megan, I am sorry, but I think you're being immature.
- 卡尔  - 这就是我们的生活
- Carl-- - This is the way we are,
不管你喜不喜欢  亲爱的
like it or not, sweetheart.
对别人撒谎来引起关注并不能解决问题
And lying to people for attention is not the way to change it.
爸  艾米和辛迪都叫我妈妈了
Amy and Cindy call me Mom, Dad.
- 她们已经叫我妈妈了  - 所以你就有权撒谎了吗
- They call me Mom! - And that gives you the right to lie?
还去报警
To call the police?
我宣布接下来的三个月孩子们
I'm placing the children with Mr. and Mrs. Lawson
跟着劳森先生和劳森太太住
for the next three months.
蒂尔登先生  你将只能在每周末和假期期间去看孩子
Mr. Tilden, you may see your daughters on weekends and holidays,
如果你能在这90内完成父母教育课程
and if, in that 90-day period, you complete a parenting class
并且接受辅导  法院会重新评估孩子们的安置问题
and begin counseling, the court will revisit this placement.
我会给你一份通过批准的辅导员和父母教育课程的清单
I'll send you a list of approved counselors and parenting classes,
下一次听证会开始之前我会联系你
and I'll contact you when your next hearing is scheduled.
我得走了
I have to go.
我真的得走了
你是否曾经和别人共用毒品货类固醇的注射器针头
Have you shared needles to inject drugs or steroids?
没有
No.
你是否在1985年4月之前输过血
Have you had a blood transfusion
或者接受输血
or received blood products before April of 1985?
没有
No.
你是否有过未采取安全措施的性交  肛交  或者口交
Have you had unprotected vaginal, anal, or oral sex?
有过
Um, yes.
好的  是哪一种
Okay. Which?
我不用回答这个问题
I don't have to answer that.
好吧
Okay.
在去年一年里  你总共有过多少伴侣
How many partners have you had in the last year?
我不清楚
Um, l-- I don't know.
你知道吗  我真的没有必要做这个
You know what? l-- I really-- I really don't need to do this.
就是这儿  看到这些名字了吗  这些名字
Right there. See the names? The names...
- 露露  - 什么事
- Lulu. - Yeah?
- 额  马克  那个有唐氏综合症的孩子  - 怎么了
- Uh, Mark, the kid with Down syndrome? - Yeah?
- 我有点事  - 什么
- I have a little problem.  What?
另一个客户遇到麻烦了  他现在需要我过去  我必须去一趟
Another client is in trouble, and he needs me immediately, and I have to go.
- 好吧  - 但是我答应了这个孩子带他去试镜的
- Okay. - I promised to take him to this audition.
总之  我给他的监护人打了电话  他正在来的路上
Anyway, I called his guardian. He's on his way here.
他一会儿就到  所以
It's gonna take him a few minutes, so, uh...
- 哦  哦  好的  - 谢谢
- Oh. Oh, okay. - Thanks.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我是露露  尼克有点事得出去一趟
I'm Lulu. Nick had to go.
他跟我说过了
He told me.
对  他必须出去一下
Yeah. He had to go.
坐吧
Have a seat.
好的
Okay.
我曾经想过杀了她
I wanted to kill her.
不会花很长时间
Wouldn't take much.
我以为
I thought...
我以为我想那样做
I thought I wanted to do that.
她死了我的日子就会轻松很多
It'd be so much easier if she were dead.
是啊  我懂
Yeah. I understand.
而且没人会知道的
And no one would even really know.
他们会知道的
They'd know.
他们会知道是你干的
They'd know you did it.
有的时候  如果你在她身边待很长时间  她会睁开眼开开四周
Sometimes, if you wait long enough, she opens her eyes and looks around.
她爸妈看到了  他们想相信
Her parents see that, and they want to believe.
他们想相信他们的女儿还活着
They want to believe that she's still in there,
她在跟他们交流
that she's communicating with them,
她还活着
that she's alive.
医生都已经说了这只是骗人的反应
I mean, the doctors'll tell you it's just a trick reflex.
我也见过
I've seen it.
我知道
And I know.
你希望身体里她还活着
的You hope there's something more going on inside her head,
但是她已经不在了
but there isn't.
她就这样了
She's like she is.
蒂尔登先生  我能为你做点什么
Mr. Tilden, what can I do?
我只是
I just...
我需要你帮我做他们要求做的事
Help me do the things they're asking of me, is all.
帮我把孩子夺回来
Help me get my kids back.
你知道吗  我觉得你说得对  过去已经过去了
You know, I think you're right. The past is prologue.
是啊
Yeah.
无论你做出什么样的决定  我都会支持你
Whatever you want to do, Lulu, I'll support you...
无论你想做什么
with whatever you want to do.
你之前说你需要时间考虑清楚你想做什么
You told me that you needed time to decide what you wanted to do.
是啊
Right.
所以你想做什么
So, what do you want?
我想成为一名父亲
I want to be a father.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
露露  听我说  我真的抱歉
Lulu, listen, I'm, uh-- I'm-- I'm just so sorry.
你这段时间肯定过得很煎熬
I mean, this has gotta be a really rough time for you.
谢谢你
Thanks.
关于凯特的事
And, uh, about Kate.
我知道你在想什么  但是你错了
I know what you're thinking, but you're wrong.
- 杰克  我   - 我喜欢她
- Jake, l-- - I like her.
我之前不是威胁你
I wasn't threatening you earlier.
- 不  就是  你在警告我  - 我只是担心  仅此而已
- Oh, you were. You were warning me. - Well, I'm concerned. That's all.
那她
Well, she's, um--
那她让我去做艾滋测试
she's asked me to take an HIV test.
- 我什么都没有跟她说  - 我不是说
- I didn't say anything to her. - I'm not implying--
- 我没有  - 不  我不是说你说了  只是
- I didn't-- - No, I'm not saying that you did. It's...
那是什么
What?
我很害怕
I'm terrified.
我是说  我之前只是想加入乡村俱乐部而已
I mean, I just-- I just wanted to join a country club, you know?
我只想被大家接受  但是
I just wanted to be accepted and--
现在
And now...
我是说  我
I mean, l-- I li--
我想跟凯特这样的女生在一起
I really like the idea of being with someone like Kate.
但是如果我
But what if--
如果我去做了艾滋测试  而且测试出来我
I mean, if I take the test, and-- and the test is--
嗯
Right.
那我从今以后就只能那样了
Then all I am is that.
我是说  我只能那样了
I mean, that's all I am.
嗨  尼克
Hey, Nick.
把  你迟到了
Ah, Dad, you're here late.
是啊  我得处理一些事
Yeah, I had to finish up some stuff.
你有时间吗
You, uh-- Do you have a second?
当然
Sure.
我  呃
l, uh...
我已经知道了
I know about the problem...
孩子的事
with-- with the baby.
好吧
Right.
我在想
Uh, well, I was, uh...
我在想如果你们把孩子生下来了
I was just thinking, if you-- if you do this,
孩子需要很多帮助
the kid's gonna need a lot of help.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
那么  你知道吗  在匹兹堡有个程序
Well, there's a-- there's a program, you know, at Pitt.
- 是国家数一数二好的  - 是吗
- It's one of the best in the country. - Right.
非常贵
Expensive.
所以我
So, l, uh...
我在想我可以在那边开户
I was thinking maybe I'd open an account over there.
每年都往账户里存点钱  为了将来
Put a little something in each year for the-- for the future.
太感谢了  爸
Oh, thanks, Dad.
嗯
Yeah.
也是时候我开始
Yeah, well it's about time I started
让你帮我花点钱了
giving you some of my damn money anyway, so...
好的
Yeah.
嗯
谢谢
Thank you.
待会儿见
See you later.
你知道吗  关于你为我做的那些安排我很抱歉
You know, I feel really badly about all the planning that you did,
又是乡村俱乐部的筹备  又帮我邀请朋友
between the country club and the invitations and...
你开什么玩笑呢  这些一点都不费事好吗
You kidding? I can do that in my sleep.
不  我应该早点告诉你的  我只是有点
No, I should've just told you sooner. I'm just kind of...
露露
Oh, Lulu.
如果可以的  帮我个忙吧
You know, if you could do something for me-- If you could--
如果你不介意的话  帮我把礼物拿到我的办公室
lf you don't mind, just, uh, drop the gifts off at my office.
露露啊
Well, Lulu--
因为我想自己来给大家写便条
Because I really want to be the one to write the notes.
- 你不用解释任何事  - 我不介意
- You shouldn't have to explain anything. - I don't mind.
凯特  我说了让我来吧
I said that I wanted to do it, Kate.
好吧
Okay.
对不起
Sorry.
真的对不起  我只是  呃
I'm really sorry. I'm just, uh...
露露
Lulu.
生一个这样的宝宝真的太
A baby like this is so...
我不知道  你知道的  当孩子不是你的时候
I don't know. You know, when-- when it's not yours,
很容易跟别人说  别要这个孩子了
it's just easy to say, ''Don't have it.''
这只会是一个麻烦  你知道吗
It's just a problem then, you know?
就好像是  你在做一个要不要避免麻烦的选择
It's like just-- It's just like you're making a choice to avoid a problem.
但是  当孩子是你的时候
But when it's your baby...
很多人会选择留住孩子
A lot of people choose these kids.
是啊  那是因为他们都在稳定的情感关系中
Yeah, but they're in committed relationships.
- 我很害怕一个人面对这些  - 尼克不想要孩子吗
- I'm afraid to do this alone. - Nick doesn't want the baby?
不  他想
No, he does.
他说了  他想当爸爸
Well, he says-- he says he wants to be a father.
- 早上好  - 早
- Good morning. - Morning.
你知道吗  昨天
Uh, you know, yesterday,
我没告诉你  但是我真的挺喜欢和马克聊天的
I didn't tell you, but I really liked talking with Mark.
他是那种越看越讨喜的人
He grows on you.
是啊  我很开心
Yeah. I enjoyed it.
今天晚一点的时候我会带他去试镜
Later today, I'm taking him to that audition.
好吧
Oh, right.
如果你想去的话
lf you want to come.
也许吧
Uh, maybe.
杰克·斯特拉卡
Jake Straka.
谢谢你  佩吉
Thank you, Peggy.
佩吉
Peggy.
谁去找一下佩吉的妈妈
Will someone please find Peggy's mother?
- 谢谢你  佩吉  - 我们走吧  佩吉
- Thank you, Peggy. - Come on, Peggy.
好的  下一位  马克·巴洛
Okay, next is Mark Barlow.
到我了
That's me.
到你了
That's you.
我不知道怎么演讲
I don't know how I go do the speech.
你知道的  马克
You know it, Mark.
我不知道
I don't know.
马克·巴罗在哪里
Mark Barlow.
能不能稍等一下
Uh, could you just give us a second, please?
喂  马克  你知道怎么演讲的  你做过的
Hey, Mark, you know the speech. You've done it.
站起来吧
Now just stand up.
加油
Come on.
看到刚才那个女孩了吗  佩吉
See that girl, Peggy?
她就站在那儿
She just stood there.
什么都没做  没关系的
She didn't say anything. So it's okay.
你只要上去告诉大家你是谁
You just go out there and tell them who you are.
好吗
Okay?
你可以的  马克  加油
You can do this, Mark. Come on.
你会演讲的  你给我做过的  还记得吗
You know the speech. You did it for me, remember?
上去告诉大家你是谁就行了
Just go up and tell them who you are.
很好
That's good.
大家好  我叫马克
Hello. I'm Mark.
我叫马克
I'm Mark.
如果我们影子
''lf we shadows''...
我
l, uh...
如果我们影子
''lf we shadows
我  冒犯
''l offended,
想想但是这  这一切都被愈合了
think but this-- this all is mended.''
很高兴你去了
Glad you could make it.
是啊  我也很开心我去了
Yeah. I'm glad that I came.
他表现得很好
He did really well.
是啊  基本上那个角色就是他了
Yeah, well, he's quite the character.
嗨
Hi.
我刚给你写了张纸条
I was just writing you a note.
这是孩子欢迎会的礼物
These are the presents from the baby shower.
对哦  我忘了你要来了  不好意思
Yeah, I forgot you were coming. Sorry.
好的  谢谢你
Right. Well, thank you.
没事
Okay.
那再见了
Well, I'll see you guys.
- 嗯  我再打给你  - 好的
- Yeah. I'll call you. - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以
So...
什么
What?
到底怎么了
What is it?
也许我们不应该把这些礼物送回去
Well, maybe we shouldn't send them back.
真的吗
Really?
你确定吗
You sure?
嗯
Yeah.
我不知道
I have no idea.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177